The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
With your cultivation,
how did you get the position of Cloud Sky Sect Leader ?
Because
she is my woman.
You're finally back.
It's the Sect Ancestor !
The Sect Ancestor is back !
That's awesome !
Ceng Niu !?
What ?
The Sect Ancestor is Ceng Niu ?!
The Ceng Niu who chopped off Red Butterfly's arm,
it's him !
So you're the one who wants to wipe out the Cloud Sky Sect…
As expected of the Ancestor !
Ceng... Ceng Niu,
I...
I didn't know you were from the Cloud Sky Sect.
This time...
This time I was reckless !
Reckless ?
Then you will pay the price of your recklessness !
Ceng Niu,
don’t push this bullying too far !
Bully ? Sure, today I'm the one bullying.
Fleeing already ?
Ceng Niu,
I've only killed a few low level disciples !
There is no death grudge between us !
Now there is.
Dao of Insects ?
That's right,
insects and beasts
are part of the laws of heaven and earth.
Heaven and earth are cruel.
If humans can eat beasts,
then beasts can also eat humans !
Seal !
That fiend is dead...
Wan'er !
Liu Fei, Song Qing,
seal the sect.
No one is allowed to leave.
Yes !
This is...
a death aura.
Senior...
Are you feeling better ?
Are you still going to leave ?
I'm not leaving.
Really ?
Really.
Wan'er,
you need to recover.
Get some rest.
What the hell is going on ?
When I left 100 years ago,
Wan'er was still fine.
Ancestor,
Elder Li failed to reach Nascent Soul 3 times.
When she last failed 30 years ago,
she almost died...
Since then
her health has been deteriorating day by day.
When I was treating Sect Leader's body,
I discovered that she overused her life energy in the past.
Hence the reduction of lifespan.
Now that the Sect Leader is at the end of her life,
she's been relying on pills to survive.
If she was an ordinary Core Formation cultivator,
she'd be long dead.
Overuse of life energy ?
The power of that jade slip was amazing...
So Wan'er used up her lifespan to make it...
Wan'er is different from Wang Zhuo.
He had reached Nascent Soul
so I could help him to be reborn.
But Wan'er is at the end of her lifespan.
If I force her reincarnation,
she won't be strong enough to avoid the law of heavens.
Now,
the only way to save her life
is to have her reach Nascent Soul.
Liu Fei,
Song Qing,
Yes !
I want to leave with Wan'er.
As of today,
you will manage the Cloud Sky Sect.
Understood !
Also,
the fact that I am Ceng Niu
must not leak.
Find a way to deal with the disciples.
Don't worry, Ancestor.
I'll erase their memories.
Lu Fei is willing to follow Ancestor
to ensure your safety.
Tie Yan is also willing.
Snowy canyon\NCountry of Chu's border
Senior Zhou Yi's told me that
the celestial jade pagoda must be placed in a Yin Energy gathering spot.
The Celestial's aura
should help Wan'er to temporarily suppress her death aura.
Although there is only a hint of domain in the pagoda,
it must not be underestimated.
Thank you Ancestor.
I owe her too much
for all these years I've been gone.
Senior...
You're awake.
What is this ?
A Senior's artifact.
When I went to the Celestial Realm,
I got to meet that Senior.
He gave it to me before his death
so that I could take care of it for 1000 years.
The Celestial Realm is such a dangerous place...
are you alright ?
I'm fine.
If you want,
I'll tell you the whole story.
So...
Zhou Yi's wife is inside that pagoda...
While he's trying to avenge her death...
I wonder how Senior Zhou Yi is after he turned into a Sword Spirit
and went to the Da Lou Sword Sect.
Whatever the outcome,
it was all his choice.
I hope his wish comes true.
This is...?
A gift for you.
Grade 5 pill recipes !
They are so expensive,
where did you get them ?
If you want,
after this,
I'll get you even more.
Thank you Senior.
Senior,
Wan'er has a favor to ask.
What is it ?
This is
The Soul Bloods of the Cloud Sky Sect.
Can you please
help me return it to them.
I'm afraid that if something happens to me,
I'll get them into trouble again.
You won't die.
Wan'er,
trust me,
I will never
let you die.
We will stay here so you can heal in peace,
I'll make sure you get better.
1 month later
From today onwards,
this place
will be our new home.
Ancestor,
we went to the Sea of Devils
to confirm that
the rank 6 pill that will be auctioned
is a Return to Origin pill.
The auction is in 7 days,
here is the invitation.
Okay.
We take our leave then.
Wait,
every Soul Formation cultivator
must understand the heavens in their own way.
The heavens are ruthless,
but you need a hint of emotion,
at least enough to move your heart.
The spiritual energy in your bodies is a mess.
The area around this pagoda is the best place for you to train.
Go 50 li away from it.
When you can get close to it with your own cultivation,
I will give you two a few more pointers.
Thank you Ancestor.
Although the celestial jade pagoda can suppress her death aura,
it's only a temporary solution.
If I could obtain this grade 6 pill,
I'm sure it'll suppress it for good
and restore Wan'er's life energy.
A grade 6 Return to Origin pill is unheard of,
I didn't expect its formula to show up in the Sea of Devils.
I'll get it,
so you can reach Nascent Soul.
Senior is leaving ?
I'll be right back,
it won't be long.
I want to go with you !
I'm much better now.
It's nothing serious.
Wan'er,
I cut off Red Butterfly's arm in the Rain Celestial Realm.
Now that I'm back on Suzaku,
she will want her revenge.
There will be a lot of people there.
This pagoda
is able to withstand attacks from Ascendant cultivators.
It's safer here.
Senior...
I don't want to leave your side ever again.
Wan'er...
Also,
there's another place in the Sea of Devils I have been thinking about.
Why is the Ancestor so happy today ?
Rumor has it that the Sea of Devils
is where Ancestor and Elder Li met.
It's a nostalgia trip,
of course they'd be happy.
The Fighting Evil Sect !
How did this happen ?
The cave was here.
It's gone...
The memories of our past
are all gone...
Senior...
Let's go.
The cave is not gone.
The Ancestor
pulled a mountain out of the ground !
Wan'er,
the cave is not gone.
An exact copy...
You brought me here back then,
saying you want to settle down
and built this cave.
I plan to stay in this cave long-term.
If the formation is broken,
I can easily escape.
But you
will have to rely on yourself.
Back then,
I made many pills here
while waiting for your return.
I remember the day you brought back a Flood Dragon.
I always wanted to ask
how you caught it.
But you were so cold...
I was afraid to ask.
And then,
I waited here for 3 years.
I didn't expect you to come back
with a bunch of people chasing you.
At that time, your formation
was able to stall enough time.
I helped you,
and then you saved me.
Senior,
why don't we stay here for a few days ?
Sure.
Senior,
what's this ?
This is the Thunder Frog I tamed.
It was seriously injured
in the Celestial Realm.
I haven't found a way to cure it yet.
These pills I made
are useless to me now.
I might as well give them to it.
It really worked !
Wan'er,
it's time to go.
Come quick !
A late stage Nascent Soul cultivator ?
Senior, it's an honor
to have you here.
This place is messy,
please follow me to the third floor.
There's no way out.
This time,
I've made lots of preparations.
Do you remember the guy
who bought the recipes a few days ago ?
Do you think he will come ?
Zi Xin\NMiddle stage Nascent Soul
Gongsun Fan\NMiddle stage Soul Formation
A Soul Formation cultivator !
This..
Who is this person ?
Hold your tongue,
the two guards are both peak Nascent Soul.
you don't want to anger them.
This pill recipe
is mine.
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust\Nlike water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,\Nthe truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death\Nare like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,\Nto cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled\Nbecause half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate\Nto ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage\Nto pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand\Nthe hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers\Nwhile prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,\Nthe law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.\NReincarnation is not to be feared.